{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238491592","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238491592"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 853567e0-2d70-41d5-bfa6-18a8249690b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_12_12-5-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238532238","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238532237"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 853567e0-2d70-41d5-bfa6-18a8249690b2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_12_12-5-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238540895","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238540894"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238543052","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238543052"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238545209","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238545209"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238548413","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238548413"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238550712","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238550711"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238552953","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238552953"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238555826","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238555826"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238558034","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238558033"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238560215","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238560215"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238563395","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238563394"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238565511","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238565510"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238567637","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238567637"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238570646","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238570645"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238572914","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238572913"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238575120","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238575120"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238578133","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238578132"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238580459","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238580459"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238582797","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238582796"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238585805","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238585804"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238587914","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238587913"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238590017","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238590016"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238593171","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238593170"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238595362","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238595361"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238597547","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238597547"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238600690","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238600689"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238603093","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238603093"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238605493","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238605493"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238608603","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238608602"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238610925","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238610925"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238613206","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238613206"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238616206","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238616205"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238618431","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238618430"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238620669","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238620669"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238623600","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238623600"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238625983","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238625982"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238628372","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238628371"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238631516","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238631515"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238633860","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238633860"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238636225","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238636225"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238639214","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238639213"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238641468","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238641467"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238642082","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238642081"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238642168","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238642168"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238648510","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238648510"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238654753","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238654753"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238661004","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238661003"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 4d53a4d0-3dd4-4156-9fd3-418a80dd5103"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238671261","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238671261"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 5a2b1ad2-622a-4ba8-a908-7ed0d9775459"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_n-f-i"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238674565","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238674565"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 5a2b1ad2-622a-4ba8-a908-7ed0d9775459"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-k-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238677521","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238677521"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 5a2b1ad2-622a-4ba8-a908-7ed0d9775459"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-u-e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238680247","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238680247"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 5a2b1ad2-622a-4ba8-a908-7ed0d9775459"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_l-y-i"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238686107","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238686107"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 5a2b1ad2-622a-4ba8-a908-7ed0d9775459"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_l-y-i"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238689498","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238689498"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 5a2b1ad2-622a-4ba8-a908-7ed0d9775459"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_d-i-a"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238692947","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238692947"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 5a2b1ad2-622a-4ba8-a908-7ed0d9775459"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_t-i-d"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238695851","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238695851"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 5a2b1ad2-622a-4ba8-a908-7ed0d9775459"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-e-l"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238698936","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238698936"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 5a2b1ad2-622a-4ba8-a908-7ed0d9775459"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_r-i-a"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238702106","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238702105"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 5a2b1ad2-622a-4ba8-a908-7ed0d9775459"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_f-i-y"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238705349","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238705349"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 5a2b1ad2-622a-4ba8-a908-7ed0d9775459"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_r-z-i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238711114","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238711114"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 5a2b1ad2-622a-4ba8-a908-7ed0d9775459"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_i_r-z-i"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238735200","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238735200"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" f6fbc985-6e11-4e7d-b8f8-864d040cc139"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_n-f-i"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238738858","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238738858"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" f6fbc985-6e11-4e7d-b8f8-864d040cc139"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_t-i-d"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238744303","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238744303"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" f6fbc985-6e11-4e7d-b8f8-864d040cc139"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-u-e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238747577","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238747577"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" f6fbc985-6e11-4e7d-b8f8-864d040cc139"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_d-i-a"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238750039","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238750038"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" f6fbc985-6e11-4e7d-b8f8-864d040cc139"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_i_d-i-a"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238766412","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238766412"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 7c3b257e-2036-42ca-8835-f704e395542e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238766634","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238766634"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 7c3b257e-2036-42ca-8835-f704e395542e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238767598","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238767597"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 7c3b257e-2036-42ca-8835-f704e395542e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238768870","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238768870"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 7c3b257e-2036-42ca-8835-f704e395542e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238771733","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238771733"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 7c3b257e-2036-42ca-8835-f704e395542e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238772577","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238772577"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 7c3b257e-2036-42ca-8835-f704e395542e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238772890","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238772890"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 7c3b257e-2036-42ca-8835-f704e395542e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238774131","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238774131"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 7c3b257e-2036-42ca-8835-f704e395542e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238775121","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238775121"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 7c3b257e-2036-42ca-8835-f704e395542e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238775172","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238775172"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 7c3b257e-2036-42ca-8835-f704e395542e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238780241","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238780241"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 7c3b257e-2036-42ca-8835-f704e395542e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238784936","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238784935"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 7c3b257e-2036-42ca-8835-f704e395542e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238790386","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238790386"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 7c3b257e-2036-42ca-8835-f704e395542e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238795379","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238795378"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 7c3b257e-2036-42ca-8835-f704e395542e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238807017","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238807016"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" b734d0d2-45b2-41a8-ab15-9afb94f8632e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jasho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JASHO"," userResponse":" JASHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238808092","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238808092"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" b734d0d2-45b2-41a8-ab15-9afb94f8632e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" jasho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238808173","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238808173"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" b734d0d2-45b2-41a8-ab15-9afb94f8632e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jasho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JASHO"," userResponse":" JASHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238813186","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238813185"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" b734d0d2-45b2-41a8-ab15-9afb94f8632e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" jasho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238821550","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238821550"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238821922","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238821922"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238822405","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238822405"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238822748","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238822748"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238823151","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238823151"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238823624","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238823624"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238823847","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238823846"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238827015","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238827015"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238827049","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238827048"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238827761","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238827761"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238828154","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238828154"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238828447","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238828447"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238828649","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238828649"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238828842","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238828842"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238829156","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238829156"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238829379","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238829379"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238832530","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238832530"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238832934","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238832934"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238835443","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238835443"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238835646","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238835646"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238835849","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238835849"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238839265","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238839265"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238842941","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238842941"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238843963","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238843963"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238846604","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238846604"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238846983","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238846983"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238847471","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238847471"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238847820","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238847820"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238848233","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238848232"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238848717","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238848717"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238848949","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238848949"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238852130","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238852130"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238852171","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238852170"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238852901","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238852900"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238853305","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238853305"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238853606","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238853605"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238853818","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238853818"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238854011","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238854011"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238854333","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238854333"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238854562","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238854562"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238857184","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238857184"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238857246","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238857246"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238862133","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238862133"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 03e46223-0283-4889-9038-6bf6aea978cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238882184","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238882183"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 572be2bd-242e-42aa-a0e3-612894a2c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_r_g"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238888839","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238888838"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 572be2bd-242e-42aa-a0e3-612894a2c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_n_j"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238895541","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238895541"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 572be2bd-242e-42aa-a0e3-612894a2c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_y_k"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238902182","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238902182"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 572be2bd-242e-42aa-a0e3-612894a2c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_s_d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238908816","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238908816"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 572be2bd-242e-42aa-a0e3-612894a2c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_j_p"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238915467","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238915467"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 572be2bd-242e-42aa-a0e3-612894a2c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_v_j_m"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238922125","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238922125"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 572be2bd-242e-42aa-a0e3-612894a2c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_r_j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238928787","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238928787"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 572be2bd-242e-42aa-a0e3-612894a2c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_j_l"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238935424","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238935424"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 572be2bd-242e-42aa-a0e3-612894a2c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_i_h"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238942071","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238942071"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 572be2bd-242e-42aa-a0e3-612894a2c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_y_w_j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238955238","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238955238"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" 572be2bd-242e-42aa-a0e3-612894a2c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_J..J.all.10.rand.say.48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_y_w_j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238965015","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238965015"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" d9ad878f-a5ad-44c9-99dc-4d72968f9bcf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550238966122","data":{"timestamp":" 1550238966121"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190215_164758"," gameId":" d9ad878f-a5ad-44c9-99dc-4d72968f9bcf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}